top10for.com 2017-11-21

# Privacy Policy -

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://top10for.com/contact-us/) here.

At top10for.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by top10for.com and how it is used.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, top10for.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

top10for.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## Amazon Associates Program

top10for.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

Note: Amazon, the Amazon logo, MYHABIT, and the MYHABIT logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on top10for.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to top10for.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
– Google Adsense  
– Commission Junction  
– Clickbank  
– Amazon Associates

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on top10for.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

top10for.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. top10for.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Note:

All your personal information that you provided or contacted to us are never leaked or sold to the third parties and they are well protected by us.

## DMCA

All pictures copyright to their respective owner(s). Top10for does not claim ownership of any of the pictures displayed on this site unless stated otherwise. Top10for does not knowingly intend or attempt to offend or violate any copyright or intellectual property rights of any entity. Some images used on Top10for are taken from the web and believed to be in the public domain. In addition, to the best of Top10for’s knowledge, all content, images, photos, etc., if any, are being used in compliance with the Fair Use Doctrine (Copyright Act of 1976, 17 U.S.C. § 107.) The pictures are provided for comment/criticism/news reporting/educational purposes only.

If you have any concern about your privacy or you don’t want us to use your photo on our site, please [contact us](http://top10for.com/contact-us/ "Click here to contact us!") now.

Best Regards,
